Guide to the Walter Strickland Thornber Papers and Photographs 1900-1915
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 2. Images
  - Subseries 2.1: Glass Plate Negatives and Photo Prints
    - Subseries 2.1.3: Photographic Prints
      - Trees in a forest with a wooden structure running along the ground., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 78)
      - A man stands on a wooden structure that runs through a forest.., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 79)
      - A man stands on the side of a mountain near a ditch that appears to be used for irrigation., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 80)
      - Men stand on the side of a mountain next to what appears to be the construction for an irrigation ditch., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 81)
      - Trees surrounding a pond with swans swimming in it., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 82)
      - Tree stump surrounded by other trees in a forest., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 83)
      - Field of some undetermined crop., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 84)
      - A group of women sits in a field., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 85)
      - An unspecified flower in a vase next to a measuring stick., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 86)
      - Men climbing a hill next to a tree in the forest., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 87)
      - A group of children sit on a pile of dirt in a field., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 88)
      - An empty field., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 89)
      - A field with piles of hay scattered through it., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 90)
      - A field with trees in the background., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 91)
      - A torn photograph of a plant with thorns on it., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 92)
      - A man stands next to a grouping of young trees., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 93)
      - A man stands in what appears to be a young orchard., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 94)
      - A tree trunk., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 95)
      - A woman stands in a boat on a pond., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 96)
      - An undetermined plant growing up a trellis., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 97)
      - An unspecified flower in a vase next to a measuring stick., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 98)
      - A group of men and women sit under a wooden structure next to a group of trees., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 99)
      - A torn photograph of an unknown plant with thorns on it., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 100)
      - Men, women, and children in a barn with wooden crates of fruit laid out on tables, Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 101)
      - Two men sitting in a field in front of a wooded area. The faces of the men are partially obscured. Torn., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 102)
      - Between rows of unknown plants at an orchard., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Unspecified plant., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - C.J. Stuart's Patent Berry Refrigerator Monroe, Wash., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Field of unspecified plants., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Between rows of unknown plants at an orchard., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Photograph of the branch of a raspberry bush., Undated; 1 items (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Subseries 2.2: Lantern Slides
    - Concrete. People working with concrete and completed concrete structures., Undated; 35 items (Box 12, Folder 1-35)
    - Agricultural cartoons. Ink drawn image of a tree being sprayed by a man with a hose., Undated; 1 items (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Agricultural cartoons. Ink drawn image of two pieces of fruit with faces dressed as a man and a woman who are holding hands., Undated; 1 items (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Agricultural cartoons. Ink drawn image of two pieces of fruit with faces dressed as a man and a woman driving in a car., Undated; 1 items (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Agricultural cartoons. Ink drawn image of a large insect chasing a man., Undated; 1 items (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Agricultural cartoons. Ink drawn image of a man sawing off a tree branch that he is sitting on., Undated; 1 items (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Agricultural cartoons. Ink drawn image of a man eating an apple with the words "An Apple You Can Eat In The Dark" written beside the image., Undated; 1 items (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Agricultural cartoons. Ink drawn image of a man laying down holding a net. A large insect stands on top of him with the words "This is the Top" written at the top of the image., Undated; 1 items (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Interiors and exteriors of homes., Undated; 68 items (Box 13, Folder 1-68)